irex.org 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy | IREX

This IREX Privacy Policy is designed to inform visitors to our website irex.org about what information we may collect and how we protect users’ privacy. We encourage you to read this privacy policy before submitting any personal information through this website. IREX reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time by posting changes on our website.

## Information we collect and how we use it

We collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide it to us. We do not give, share, sell, or transfer any personal information to a third party without your permission.

Forms on our “Contact Us,” subscription, donation, and career pages may ask for information such as name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card information, and other personally identifiable information. However, we do not store sensitive personal information such as credit card or Social Security numbers.

## Internet Protocol (IP) address

IREX may track visitors’ computer IP addresses, while each user’s personal information remains completely anonymous. This can help us diagnose server problems, administer our website, and analyze user interest, which is information that we may use to enhance visitors’ experience.

## Cookies

Our website uses cookies, pieces of information transferred to computers when browsing websites. This is standard practice, and your browser is probably set to accept cookies.

If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can opt out by changing your browser's settings. Here are instructions for [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en), [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences), [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies), and [Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac).

## Security

Information provided by users of the IREX website is stored in a modern hosting facility providing industry-standard facility and data protection. However, users should be aware that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure.

## Unsubscribing

IREX will remove your contact information from our e-mail lists (or other lists) at any time upon request. E-mails to users who have submitted information through our website include instructions for removing that information from our database.

## Other websites

Our website contains links to other sites. If you click one of these links, you will leave IREX's website, and your information is no longer subject to this privacy policy.

_For questions about this privacy policy, please contact[communications@irex.org](mailto:communications@irex.org)._
